Finding Aid for Michigan Interscholastic Forensic Association records
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Activities 1943-2006
  - Debate
    - Class C-D District Reports and Records 1986/87, 3 folders (Box 29)
    - Class A At-Large Petitions 1986/87 (Box 29)
    - Class B At-Large Petitions 1986/87 (Box 29)
    - Class C-D At-Large Petitions 1986/87 (Box 29)
    - Class A District Reports and Records 1987/88, 5 folders (Box 29)
    - Class B District Reports and Records 1987/88, 4 folders (Box 29)
    - Class C-D District Reports and Records 1987/88, 2 folders (Box 29)
    - Class A District Reports and Records 1988/89, 5 folders (Box 29)
    - Class B District Reports and Records 1988/89, 4 folders (Box 29)
    - Class C-D District Reports and Records 1988/89, 2 folders (Box 29)
    - Class A At-Large Petitions 1988/89 (Box 29)
    - Class B At-Large Petitions 1988/89 (Box 29)
    - Class C-D At-Large Petitions 1988/89 (Box 29)
    - Class A District Reports and Records 1989/90, 5 folders (Box 29)
    - Class B District Reports and Records 1989/90, 3 folders (Box 29)
    - Class C-D District Reports and Records 1989/90, 2 folders (Box 29)
    - Class A At-Large Petitions 1989/90 (Box 29)
    - Class B At-Large Petitions 1989/90 (Box 29)
    - Class C-D At-Large Petitions 1989/90 (Box 29)
    - Class A District Reports and Records 1990/91, 5 folders (Box 30)
    - Class B District Reports and Records 1990/91, 3 folders (Box 30)
    - Class C-D District Reports and Records 1990/91, 2 folders (Box 30)
    - Class A At-Large Petitions 1990/91 (Box 30)
    - Class A District Reports and Records 1991/92, 6 folders (Box 30)
    - Class B District Reports and Records 1991/92, 4 folders (Box 30)
    - Class C-D District Reports and Records 1991/92, 2 folders (Box 30)
    - Class A At-Large Petitions 1991/92 (Box 30)
    - Class B At-Large Petitions 1991/92 (Box 30)
    - Class C-D At-Large Petitions 1991/92 (Box 30)
    - Class A District Reports and Records 1992/93, 5 folders (Box 30)
    - Class B District Reports and Records 1992/93, 4 folders (Box 30)
    - Class C-D District Reports and Records 1992/93, 2 folders (Box 30)
    - Class A District Reports and Records 1993/94, 5 folders (Box 30)
    - Class B District Reports and Records 1993/94, 4 folders (Box 30)
    - Class C-D District Reports and Records 1993/94, 2 folders (Box 30)
    - Class A At-Large Petitions 1993/94 (Box 30)
    - Class B At-Large Petitions 1993/94 (Box 30)
    - Class C-D At-Large Petitions 1993/94 (Box 30)
    - Class A District Reports and Records 1994/95, 5 folders (Box 30)
    - Class B District Reports and Records 1994/95, 3 folders (Box 30)
    - Class C-D District Reports and Records 1994/95, 2 folders (Box 30)
    - Class A At-Large Petitions 1994/95 (Box 30)
    - Class B At-Large Petitions 1994/95 (Box 30)
    - Class C-D At-Large Petitions 1994/95 (Box 30)
    - Class A District Reports and Records 1995/96 (Box 31)
    - Class B District Reports and Records 1995/96 (Box 31)
    - Class C-D District Reports and Records 1995/96 (Box 31)
    - At-Large Petitions -- All Classes 1995/96 (Box 31)
    - Class A District Reports and Records 1996/97, 5 folders (Box 31)
    - Class B District Reports and Records 1996/97, 3 folders (Box 31)
    - Class C-D District Reports and Records 1996/97, 2 folders (Box 31)
    - At-Large Petitions -- All Classes 1996/97 (Box 31)
    - Class A District Reports and Records 1997/98, 5 folders (Box 31)
    - Class B District Reports and Records 1997/98, 4 folders (Box 31)
    - Class C-D District Reports and Records 1997/98, 2 folders (Box 31)
    - Class A At-Large Petitions 1997/98 (Box 31)
    - Class B At-Large Petitions 1997/98 (Box 31)
    - Class C-D At-Large Petitions 1997/98 (Box 31)
    - Class A District Reports and Records 1998/99, 6 folders (Box 31)
    - Class B District Reports and Records 1998/99 (3 folders (Box 31)
    - Class C-D District Reports and Records 1998/99, 2 folders (Box 31)
    - Class A At-Large Petitions 1998/99 (Box 31)
    - Class B At-Large Petitions 1998/99 (Box 31)
    - Class C-D At-Large Petitions 1998/99 (Box 31)
    - Class A District Reports and Records 1999/00, 5 folders (Box 32)
    - Class B District Reports and Records 1999/00, 3 folders (Box 32)
    - Class C-D District Reports and Records 1999/00, 2 folders (Box 32)
    - District Division Advancements 2001/02 (Box 32)
    - Division I District Reports and Records 2001/02, 3 folders (Box 32)
    - Division II District Reports and Records 2001/02, 3 folders (Box 32)
    - Division III District Reports and Records 2001/02, 3 folders (Box 32)
    - Division I At-Large Petitions 2001/02 (Box 32)
    - Division II At-Large Petitions 2001/02 (Box 32)
    - District Division Advancements 2002/03 (Box 32)
    - Division I District Reports and Records 2002/03, 3 folders (Box 32)
    - Division II District Reports and Records 2002/03, 3 folders (Box 32)
    - Division III District Reports and Records 2002/03, 3 folders (Box 32)
    - Division I District Reports and Records 2003/04, 3 folders (Box 32)
    - Division II District Reports and Records 2003/04, 3 folders (Box 32)
    - Division III District Reports and Records 2003/04, 3 folders (Box 32)
    - Division I At-Large Petitions 2003/04 (Box 32)
    - Division I District Reports and Records 2004/05, 3 folders (Box 32)
    - Division II District Reports and Records 2004/05, 3 folders (Box 32)
    - Division III District Reports and Records 2004/05, 3 folders (Box 32)
    - State Debate 1964/65 (Box 33)
    - State Debate 1969/70-2005/06, 38 folders (Box 33)
    - John S. Knight Contests -- Assorted Correspondence 1969-1988, 2 folders (Box 34)
    - John S. Knight At-Large Bids 1992/93 (Box 34)
    - John S. Knight At-Large Bids 1994/95-1999/00, 7 folders (Box 34)
    - John S. Knight At-Large Bids 2004/05 (Box 34)
    - John S. Knight Ballot Forms circa 1967-1976 (Box 34)
    - John S. Knight Certificates 1963, undated (Box 34)
    - John S. Knight Contests -- Assorted Newspaper Articles 1961-1992 (Box 34)
    - John S. Knight Contest Brochures (Box 34)
    - John S. Knight Contests -- Financial Correspondence 1975-1993 (Box 34)
    - John S. Knight Contests -- Financial Summaries 1973-1992 (Box 34)
    - John S. Knight Contest Procedures 1968-1973 (Box 34)
    - John S. Knight Contest Registration 1992/93 (Box 34)
    - John S. Knight Contest Registration 1994/95 (Box 34)
    - John S. Knight Contest Registration 1996/97, 1997/98, 2 folders (Box 34)
    - John S. Knight Contests -- Rules Modifications/Suggestions 1973-2001 (Box 34)
    - John S. Knight Contests -- Scholarship Fund Issues 1973-1999 (Box 34)
    - John S. Knight Contests -- Speeches, Descriptive Aids (Box 34)
    - John S. Knight Contestant Mailings 1980s (Box 34)
    - John S. Knight Death 1981 (Box 34)
    - John S. Knight Participants 1961-1975 (Box 34)
    - John S. Knight Qualifiers -- Eligibility/Participation Issues 1975-1993 (Box 34)
    - John S. Knight Scholarship Contests 1956-1961 (Box 34)
    - John S. Knight Scholarship Contests 1967-1974 (Box 34)
    - John S. Knight Scholarship Contests 1974/75-1988/89, 16 folders (Box 34)
    - John S. Knight Scholarship Contests 1990/91-2002/03, 13 folders (Box 34)
    - John S. Knight Scholarship Contests 50th Anniversary Materials 1997, 4 folders (Box 34)
    - 50th Anniversary Debates 1967 (Box 35)
    - 75th Anniversary Committee 1991 (Box 35)
    - Annual Debate Topic Selections 1969-2006 (Box 35)
    - Article on Educational Advantages of Debate 1930 (Box 35)
    - Bicentennial Youth Debates 1974-1976 (Box 35)
    - Bound Materials -- "Former Championship Debaters" (Box 35)
    - Debate Administrative Handbook Draft 1984 (Box 35)
    - Debate Awards -- Various Newspaper Clippings 1968 (Box 35)
    - Debate -- Ballot Problems 1984-2002 (Box 35)
    - Debate Bibliographies 1967-1969 (Box 35)
    - Debate Briefs 1951/52-1963/64 (Box 35)
    - Debate Certificate Examples (Box 35)
    - Debate Coaches Association circa 1964-1965 (Box 35)
    - Debate -- Complaints, Concerns, Protests 1969-2003 (Box 35)
    - Debate Contract Samples 1950s (Box 35)
    - Debate in Detroit Public Schools 1985-1989 (Box 35)
    - Debate FAQs 2000/01 (Box 35)
    - Debate Handbook Edits (Box 35)
    - Debate Judge Certification, 6 folders (Box 35)
    - Debate -- Judge Information Sheets (Box 35)
    - Debate -- Judging Issues (Box 35)
    - Debate Judge Survey circa 1975 (Box 35)
    - Debate -- Library Theft 1980/81 (Box 35)
    - Debate Modifications Questionnaires (Box 35)
    - Debate -- Proposals, Rules Interpretations/Modifications 1969-2000 (Box 35)
    - Debate Questionnaires 1952-1959 (Box 35)
    - Debate -- Rules Summaries and Revisions 1980-1982 (Box 35)
    - Debate -- Sponsorship and Publicity Ideas 1986-1987 (Box 35)
    - Debate Survey 2001/02 (Box 35)
    - Detroit Free Press Correspondence, 1967- circa 1995, 2 folders (Box 35)
    - Detroit Free Press Debate Article Samples 1988-1993 (Box 35)
    - Detroit Free Press Debate Budgets (Box 35)
    - Detroit Free Press Merit Certificate Forms (Box 35)
    - District Debate -- Eligibility/Participation Correspondence 1972-2005 (Box 35)
    - Districts Restructuring 2001/02 (Box 35)
    - District Debate -- Scheduling Issues 1972-2000 (Box 35)
    - Draft of Debate Article 1996 (Box 35)
    - Elice Howard Award 1998 (Box 35)
    - Lists of Detroit Free Press Debate Awardees, 1936-1960/61 (Box 35)
    - Mailings for District/Regional Tournaments and District Structures 1964-2005, 2 folders (Box 35)
    - Mailing Lists -- Directors of Debate 1967-1969 (Box 35)
    - National Bicentennial Debates 1974-1976 (Box 35)
    - Proclamations of Enlightenment (Box 35)
    - Schedules and Forms for Forensic Day/State Debates and Banquets 1952-1961 (Box 35)
    - Speech by Detroit Free Press Staff Member 1981 (Box 35)
    - State Debates -- Assorted Newspaper Articles 1936-1993 (Box 35)
    - State Debates -- At-Large Bids 1985-2005 (Box 35)
    - State Debate Correspondence 1976-1979 (Box 35)
    - State Debates -- Format Proposals and Modifications 1970-2006 (Box 35)
    - State Debates -- Mailings 2005 (Box 35)
    - State Debate Procedures 1938-1943 (Box 35)
    - State Debates -- Videotape Orders 1974 (Box 35)
    - Statements about Debate -- Various University of Michigan Officials 1952 (Box 35)
    - Summary Lists of Championship Debate Schools 1918-1963 (Box 35)
    - Summary Lists of Debate Topics (Box 35)
    - Topic Analysis Outlines and Audiotape Orders 1983-1998 (Box 35)
    - Tournament Questionnaire 1979/80 (Box 35)
    - University of Michigan High School Debate Institute, 3 folders (Box 35)
    - Upper Peninsula Debate 1957-1985 (Box 35)
    - Upper Peninsula Debate Banquets 1951-1981 (Box 35)
  - Individual Events
    - Middle Level Tournaments 1973/74-1997/98, 24 folders (Box 36)
    - Middle Level Tournaments 1998/99, 2 folders (Box 36)
    - Middle Level Tournaments 1999/00, 2 folders (Box 36)
    - Middle Level Tournaments 2000/01 (Box 37)
    - Middle Level Tournaments 2001/02, 2 folders (Box 37)
    - Middle Level Tournaments 2002/03-2005/06, 3 folders (Box 37)
    - Middle Level -- Initial Survey, Tournaments, and Correspondence 1972-1974 (Box 37)
    - Middle Level -- Correspondence 1974-1977 (Box 37)
    - Middle Level -- Correspondence -- Awards/Awards Assemblies 1980-2001 (Box 37)
    - Middle Level -- Correspondence -- Enrollment/Membership 1975-1981 (Box 37)
    - Middle Level -- Correspondence -- Tournament Issues 1976-2000 (Box 37)
    - Middle Level -- Covington Multiple 2004 (Box 37)
    - Middle Level -- Upper Peninsula Tournaments circa 1991-1996 (Box 37)
    - Middle Level -- Advisory Committee Materials, Budget Summary 1974-1977 (Box 37)
    - Middle Level -- Survey Results 1999 (Box 37)
    - Middle Level -- Assorted Forms and Mailings (Box 37)
    - Middle Level -- Assorted Judging Instructions (Box 37)
    - Middle Level -- Tournament Results Synopses (Box 37)
    - Middle Level -- Tournament Participants/Schedules/ Notes (Box 37)
    - Middle Level -- Extemp Topics 1975-1986 (Box 37)
    - Middle Level -- Extemp Topics 1987-2004 (Box 37)
    - Middle Level -- Impromptu Topics 1973-1986 (Box 37)
    - Middle Level -- Impromptu Topics 1987-2002 (Box 37)
    - Middle Level -- Bibliographies 1983-1994 (Box 37)
    - Middle Level -- Invitation Cover Letters (Box 37)
    - Middle Level -- Tournament Invitation Packets 1975-1989 (Box 37)
    - Middle Level -- Tournament Invitation Packets 1990-1998 (Box 37)
    - Middle Level -- Tournament Invitation Packets 1998-2005 (Box 37)
    - Middle Level -- Tournament Confirmation Cover Letters (Box 37)
    - Middle Level -- Tournament Confirmation Packets (Box 37)
    - Middle Level -- Tournament Specifics (Box 37)
    - Middle Level -- Judge Competence Form (Box 37)
    - Middle Level -- Entry/Registration Form (Box 37)
    - Middle Level -- Post Tournament Letters (Box 37)
    - Middle Level -- Judge Information (Box 37)
    - Middle Level -- General Fall Cover Letters (Box 37)
    - Middle Level -- General Fall Packets (Box 37)
    - Middle Level -- Spring Member Mailings (Box 37)
    - Middle Level -- Membership Confirmation Mailings (Box 37)
    - Middle Level -- Membership Confirmation Cover Letters (Box 37)
    - Middle Level -- Principal Marketing Letter (Box 37)
    - Middle Level -- No Rejoin Principal Letter (Box 37)
    - District Results; Forensic Chairman Forms 1969 (Box 38)
    - Regional Chairman's Reports and Results 1970 (Box 38)
    - Lists of Regional Qualifiers for State Finals; Assorted District Results 1971 (Box 38)
    - Information on Various District and Regional Tournaments 1970-1972 (Box 38)
    - Lists of District Results 1972-1973 (Box 38)
    - Regional Results 1974 (Box 38)
    - Regional Reports; Awards Summary 1974/75 (Box 38)
    - District 4 Results 1976 (Box 38)
    - Regional Reports and Results 1975/76 (Box 38)
    - District Information; Regional Results; Awards Summary 1976/77 (Box 38)
    - District Tournament Information and Results; Regional Tournament Information 1977/78 (Box 38)
    - Region III Results 1977/78 (Box 38)
    - Region III Results 1978/79 (Box 38)
    - District and Regional Results; Awards Summary 1978/79 (Box 38)
    - District Results and Reports 1979/80, 3 folders (Box 38)
    - Regional Results 1979/80, 2 folders (Box 38)
    - District Results; Regional Awards 1980/81, 2 folders (Box 38)
    - District Tournament Information 1981/82 (Box 38)
    - Region III, District 3 Results 1982/83 (Box 38)
    - District Tournament Information; Regional Reports and Results 1982/83 (Box 38)
    - Regional Results 1983/84, 6 folders (Box 38)
    - Regional Reports 1983/84 (Box 38)
    - District Reports 1984/85, 2 folders (Box 38)
    - Regional Results 1984/85, 6 folders (Box 38)
    - Regional Reports 1984/85 (Box 38)
    - District Returns 1985/86 (Box 38)
    - District Results 1985/86, 3 folders (Box 38)
    - Regional Results 1985/86, 6 folders (Box 38)
    - Region II, District 2 Results 1986/87 (Box 38)
    - Regional Results 1986/87, 6 folders (Box 38)
    - District Results 1987/88, 6 folders (Box 38)
    - District Results 1988/89, 29 folders (Box 39)
    - Regional Results and Reports 1988/89, 6 folders (Box 39)
    - District/Regional Materials Certification Forms 1988/89 (Box 39)
    - District Results 1989/90, 29 folders (Box 39)
    - Regional Results and Reports 1989/90 (Box 39)
    - District/Regional Materials Certification Forms 1989/90 (Box 39)
    - District Results 1990/91, 28 folders (Box 39)
    - At-Large Bids to Regionals 1990/91 (Box 39)
    - Regional Results 1990/91, 6 folders (Box 39)
    - At-Large Bids to State 1990/91 (Box 39)
    - District Results 1991/92, 28 folders (Box 39)
    - At-Large Bids to Regionals 1991/92 (Box 39)
    - Regional Results 1991/92 (Box 39)
    - At-Large Bids to State 1991/92 (Box 39)
    - District Results 1992/93, 28 folders (Box 40)
    - At-Large Bids to Regionals 1992/93 (Box 40)
    - Regional Results 1992/93 (Box 40)
    - At-Large Bids to State 1992/93 (Box 40)
    - District Results 1993/94, 28 folders (Box 40)
    - At-Large Bids to Regionals 1993/94 (Box 40)
    - Regional Results 1993/94 (Box 40)
    - At-Large Bids to State 1993/94 (Box 40)
    - District Results 1994/95, 6 folders (Box 40)
    - At-Large Bids to Regionals 1994/95 (Box 40)
    - Regional Results 1994/95, 6 folders (Box 40)
    - At-Large Bids to State 1994/95 (Box 40)
    - District and Regional Results 1995/96, 6 folders (Box 40)
    - At-Large Bids to Regionals 1995/96 (Box 40)
    - At-Large Bids to State 1995/96 (Box 40)
    - Class A District Results 1996/97, 3 folders (Box 41)
    - Class BCD District Results 1996/97, 4 folders (Box 41)
    - Upper Peninsula District Results 1996/97 (Box 41)
    - At-Large Bids to Regionals 1996/97 (Box 41)
    - Class A Regional Results 1996/97, 3 folders (Box 41)
    - Class BCD Regional Results 1996/97, 3 folders (Box 41)
    - Upper Peninsula Regional Results 1996/97 (Box 41)
    - At-Large Bids to State 1996/97 (Box 41)
    - Upper Peninsula District Results 1997/98, 4 folders (Box 41)
    - Class A District Results 1997/98, 12 folders (Box 41)
    - Class BCD District Results 1997/98, 16 folders (Box 41)
    - At-Large Bids to Regionals 1997/98 (Box 41)
    - Class A Regional Results 1997/98, 3 folders (Box 41)
    - At-Large Bids to State 1997/98 (Box 41)
    - Class A District Results 1998/99, 12 folders (Box 41)
    - Class BCD District Results 1998/99, 20 folders (Box 41)
    - At-Large Bids to Regionals 1998/99 (Box 41)
    - Class A Regional Results 1998/99, 4 folders (Box 41)
    - Class BCD Regional Results 1998/99, 5 folders (Box 41)
    - At-Large Bids to State 1998/99 (Box 41)
    - Class A District Results 1999/00, 12 folders (Box 42)
    - Class BCD District Results 1999/00, 18 folders (Box 42)
    - At-Large Bids to Regionals 1999/00 (Box 42)
    - Class A Regional Results 1999/00, 4 folders (Box 42)
    - Class BCD Regional Results 1999/00, 5 folders (Box 42)
    - Class A Regional Qualifiers 1999/00, 3 folders (Box 42)
    - Upper Peninsula Qualifiers 1999/00 (Box 42)
    - Class BCD Regional Qualifiers 1999/00, 4 folders (Box 42)
    - Class A District Results 2000/01, 11 folders (Box 42)
    - Class BCD District Results 2000/01, 15 folders (Box 42)
    - At-Large Bids to Regionals 2000/01 (Box 42)
    - Class A Regional Results 2000/01, 4 folders (Box 42)
    - Class BCD Regional Results 2000/01, 5 folders (Box 42)
    - At-Large Bids to State 2000/01 (Box 42)
    - Certification Forms 2000/01, 2 folders (Box 42)
    - Class A District Results 2001/02, 12 folders (Box 42)
    - Class BCD District Results 2001/02, 12 folders (Box 42)
    - Upper Peninsula District Results 2001/02, 3 folders (Box 42)
    - At-Large Bids to Regionals 2001/02 (Box 42)
    - Class A Regional Results 2001/02, 4 folders (Box 42)
    - Class BCD Regional Results 2001/02, 5 folders (Box 42)
    - At-Large Bids to State 2001/02 (Box 42)
    - Class A District Results 2002/03, 12 folders (Box 43)
    - Upper Peninsula District Results 2002/03, 3 folders (Box 43)
    - Class BCD District Results 2002/03, 12 folders (Box 43)
    - At-Large Bids to Regionals 2002/03 (Box 43)
    - Class A Regional Results 2002/03, 4 folders (Box 43)
    - Class BCD Regional Results 2002/03, 4 folders (Box 43)
    - At-Large Bids to State 2002/03 (Box 43)
    - Class A District Results 2003/04, 12 folders (Box 43)
    - Class BCD District Results 2003/04, 15 folders (Box 43)
    - Class A Regional Results 2003/04, 4 folders (Box 43)
    - District and Regional Groupings, 1956-1969/70 (Box 43)
    - District and Regional Structures 1968/69-1998/99 (Box 43)
    - Detroit News Regional Awards Summaries 1974/75-1978/79 (Box 43)
    - Tournament Mailings to I.E. Directors 1981/82-1997/98, 2 folders (Box 43)
    - Mailings -- District Tournament Details, 1970s-1995/96, 2 folders (Box 43)
    - Mailings -- Regional Tournament Details, 1970s-1996/97, 3 folders (Box 43)
    - Assorted Undated Forms and District/Regional Information, 1963-1970s (Box 43)
    - Scripts -- Informative Speaking 1989/90 (Box 44)
    - Scripts -- Oratory 1989/90 (Box 44)
    - Scripts -- Sales 1990 (Box 44)
    - Scripts -- Storytelling (A) 1991/92 (Box 44)
    - Scripts -- Prose 1991/92 (Box 44)
    - Scripts -- Informative Speaking 1992/93 (Box 44)
    - Scripts -- Multiple Interpretation 1992/93 (Box 44)
    - Scripts -- Storytelling 1993 (Box 44)
    - Scripts -- Prose 1993 (Box 44)
    - Scripts -- Multiple Interpretation 1993 (Box 44)
    - Scripts -- Duo Interpretation 1993 (Box 44)
    - Scripts -- Multiple Interpretation 1993/94 (Box 44)
    - Scripts -- Poetry 1993/94 (Box 44)
    - Scripts -- Storytelling 1993/94 (Box 44)
    - Scripts -- Prose 1993/94 (Box 44)
    - Scripts -- Duo Interpretation 1993/94 (Box 44)
    - Scripts -- Dramatic Interpretation 1993/94 (Box 44)
    - Scripts -- Informative Speaking 1994 (Box 44)
    - Scripts -- Multiple Interpretation 1994/95 (Box 44)
    - Scripts -- Duo Interpretation 1994/95, 2 folders (Box 44)
    - Scripts -- Dramatic Interpretation 1994/95 (Box 44)
    - Scripts -- Storytelling 1994/95 (Box 44)
    - Scripts -- Prose 1994/95 (Box 44)
    - Scripts -- Poetry 1994/95 (Box 44)
    - Scripts -- Informative Speaking 1995 (Box 44)
    - Scripts -- Sales, 1995-96 (Box 44)
    - Scripts -- Multiple Interpretation 1995/96 (Box 44)
    - Scripts -- Storytelling 1995/96 (Box 44)
    - Scripts -- Prose 1995/96, 2 folders (Box 44)
    - Scripts -- Dramatic Interpretation 1995/96 (Box 44)
    - Scripts -- Duo Interpretation 1995/96 (Box 44)
    - Scripts -- Poetry 1995/96 (Box 44)
    - Scripts -- Multiple Interpretation 1996/97 (Box 44)
    - Scripts -- Prose (A) 1996/97 (Box 44)
    - Scripts -- Poetry (A) 1996/97 (Box 44)
    - Scripts -- Duo Interpretation (A) 1996/97 (Box 44)
    - Scripts -- Storytelling (A) 1996/97 (Box 44)
    - Scripts -- Dramatic Interpretation (A) 1996/97 (Box 44)
    - Scripts -- Oratory (A) 1996/97 (Box 44)
    - Scripts -- Multiple Interpretation (B) 1996/97 (Box 44)
    - Scripts -- Prose (BCD) 1996/97 (Box 44)
    - Scripts -- Poetry (BCD) 1996/97, 2 folders (Box 44)
    - Scripts -- Storytelling (BCD) 1996/97 (Box 44)
    - Scripts -- Prose (A) 1997/98, 2 folders (Box 44)
    - Scripts -- Poetry (A) 1997/98 (Box 44)
    - Scripts -- Multiple Interpretation (A) 1997/98, 2 folders (Box 44)
    - Scripts -- Storytelling (A) 1997/98, 2 folders (Box 44)
    - Scripts -- Duo Interpretation Open (A) 1997/98 (Box 45)
    - Scripts -- Duo Interpretation 9/10(A), 1997/98 (Box 45)
    - Scripts -- Dramatic Interpretation (A) 1997/98 (Box 45)
    - Scripts -- Prose (BCD) 1997/98, 2 folders (Box 45)
    - Scripts -- Storytelling (BCD) 1997/98, 2 folders (Box 45)
    - Scripts -- Dramatic Interpretation (BCD) 1997/98 (Box 45)
    - Scripts -- Multiple Interpretation (BCD) 1997/98, 2 folders (Box 45)
    - Scripts -- Duo Interpretation Open (BCD) 1997/98 (Box 45)
    - Scripts -- Duo Interpretation 9/10(BCD), 199798 (Box 45)
    - Scripts -- Poetry (BCD) 1997/98 (Box 45)
    - Scripts -- Poetry (ABCD) 1997/98 (Box 45)
    - Scripts -- Dramatic Interpretation (A) 1998/99 (Box 45)
    - Scripts -- Duo Interpretation (A) 1998/99 (Box 45)
    - Scripts -- Informative Speaking (A) 1998/99 (Box 45)
    - Scripts -- Oratory Open (A) 1998/99 (Box 45)
    - Scripts -- Oratory 9/10(A), 1998/99 (Box 45)
    - Scripts -- Poetry (A) 1998/99 (Box 45)
    - Scripts -- Prose Open (A) 1998/99 (Box 45)
    - Scripts -- Prose 9/10(A), 1998/99 (Box 45)
    - Scripts -- Multiple Interpretation (A) 1998/99 (Box 45)
    - Scripts -- Sales (A) 1998/99 (Box 45)
    - Scripts -- Storytelling (A) 1998/99 (Box 45)
    - Scripts -- Duo Interpretation (BCD) 1998/99 (Box 45)